pinkygirlgames.com 2017-11-21

# Privacy Policy

Pinkygirls.com is a free online service provider in the games domain. We provide this privacy policy in order to inform you the term and conditions we follow concerning collection of personal information and its usage. This is applicable only to the information that is gathered when you use our services. Through your access to our website you are consenting for the collection of information which is essential for us to know your demographic information and the number of pages you visit on our website. 

**Cookies**

Cookies are small text files which are very helpful for us to remember the preferences of the visitor. They store your activities on the website in order provide effective service every time you visit us. No personal information is stored into cookies which the visitors share with us. 

**Third party website**

We can't take any responsibility for the collection of any information by the third parties who have links with our website and also for their in appropriate contents. If you make use of their services or purchase some products, they may collect your personal information for the payment of goods and services. 

**Change of privacy policy**

We have all the rights to change our privacy when we deem it necessary and you will be notified whenever the change takes place. 

**Security**

The information that we collect will not be misused and shared with anyone. We respect the privacy of our visitors. Pinkygirlgames.com will make sure that this is a safe place for children to fun and enjoyment. No supervision is required for visiting our website. 

﻿
